Finding Aid for Penn Central Transportation Company Records 1835-1981
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- New York Central Railroad Company, 1835-1981; 116 linear feet
  - New York Central Railroad Company: Subsidiaries
    - South Eastern Michigan Railway Company
      - Articles of Association, 1871 (Box 150)
      - Minutes, July-October 1871 (Box 150)
    - State Line and Middlesex Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association and Dissolution, 1887-1892 (Box 150)
      - Minutes, 1887-1891; 1 volumes (Box 150)
    - Stewart Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association and Correspondence, 1887 (Box 150)
      - Minutes
        - Board of Directors
          - 1887-1926, 1 volumes (Box 150)
          - 1927-1963 (Box 290)
        - Stockholders' Annual Meeting
          - 1911, 1916-1960; 5 folders (Box 150)
          - 1961-1963 (Box 290)
    - Streator and Clinton Railroad Company
      - Articles of Incorporation and Bylaws, 1899 (Box 151)
      - Minutes, 1899-1900; 1 volumes (Box 151)
      - Miscellaneous, 1900-1908; 1939 (Box 151)
    - Sturgis, Goshen, and Saint Louis Railway Company
      - Articles of Incorporation, 1889-1915 (Box 151)
      - Minutes, 1889-1915 (Volume 52)
    - Swan Creek Railway Company of Toledo
      - Certificate of Incorporation, 1875 (Box 151)
      - Minutes, 1875-1914; 1 volumes (Box 151)
    - Terminal Railroad Company
      - Minutes
        - 1896-1902, 1 volumes (Box 151)
        - (duplicate; typed), 1896-1902 (Box 151)
      - Mortgage, 1896-1897; 1918-1920; 1939 (Box 151)
    - Three Hundred Park Avenue, Inc
      - Minutes: Annual Meeting, 1933 (Box 151)
    - Toledo and Michigan Belt Railway
      - Articles of Incorporation and Correspondence, 1881 (Box 152)
      - Deed of Conveyance, 1897; 1911-1913 (Box 152)
      - Land Book, 1887-1896 (Box 152)
      - Minutes, 1887-1897; 1 volumes (Box 152)
    - Toledo and Michigan Railway Company
      - Articles of Incorporation (certified 1919), 1882 (Box 152)
    - Toledo and Milwaukee Railway Company
      - Articles of Association, 1879 (Box 152)
    - Toledo and Ohio Northern Railway Company
      - Articles of Association, 1880 (Box 152)
      - Minutes
        - 1881, 1 volumes (Box 152)
        - 1890-1898, 1 volumes (Box 152)
      - Subscription List, 1880; 2 volumes (Box 152)
    - Toledo, Canada Southern and Detroit Railway Company
      - Articles of Consolidation and Miscellaneous, 1872; 1934 (Box 152)
      - Miscellaneous, 1872; 1906; 1956-1957 (Box 152)
        (See also: Toledo and Michigan Belt Railway Company, Deed of Conveyance 1897, 1911-1913)
    - Toledo, Norwalk and Cleveland Railroad Company
      - Incorporation Act, 1850-1851 (Box 153)
      - Minutes
        - Board of Directors, 1850-1853; 1 volumes (Box 153)
        - Commissioners and Shareholders, 1850-1853 (Box 153)
        - Executive Committee, July 15, 1853 (Box 153)
          (See: Cleveland and Toledo Railroad Company, Minutes, 1853-1869.)
    - Toledo Terminal Railroad Company (Box 153)
      (See: Pennsylvania Railroad Company: Subsidiaries--Toledo Terminal Railroad Company)
    - Union Railroad Company
      - Correspondence, 1878-1911 (scattered) (Box 153)
      - Minutes, 1852-1904; 1 volumes (Box 153)
    - Warren and Venango Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association, 1871 (Box 153)
      - Ledger, General, 1877-1881 (Volume 53)
      - Minutes, 1871-1872; 1 volumes (Box 153)
      - Mortgages, 1872; 1911 (Box 153)
      - Stock Register, 1871-1872; 1 volumes (Box 153)
    - Western Air Line Construction Company
      - Minutes, 1881-1890 (Box 154)
    - Western Transit Company
      - Articles of Incorporation, 1883-1924 (Box 154)
      - Journal, General
        - 1892-1894 (Volume 54)
        - 1894-1896 (Volume 55)
        - 1896-1898 (Volume 56)
        - 1897-1899 (Volume 57)
        - 1899-1902 (Volume 58)
        - 1906-1912 (Volume 59)
        - 1912-1921 (Volume 60)
        - 1913-1914 (Volume 61)
        - 1922-1924 (Volume 62)
      - Ledger, General
        - 1891-1897 (Volume 63)
        - 1894-1896 (Volume 64)
        - 1897 (Volume 65)
        - 1898-1900 (Volume 66)
        - 1902-1905 (Volume 67)
        - 1903-1907 (Volume 68)
        - 1912-1914 (Volume 69)
        - 1913-1921 (Volume 70)
        - 1922 (Volume 71)
      - Minutes
        - December 1883-January 1900, 1 volumes (Box 154)
        - June 1900-October 1915, 1 volumes (Box 154)
        - January 1916-April 1924, 1 volumes (Box 154)
      - Mortgage, 1886 (Box 154)
    - Western Transportation Company
      - Minutes, 1875-1889 (Volume 72)
    - Wheeling and Cleveland Railroad Company
      - Minutes, 1895-1901; 1 volumes (Box 154)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1847-1966; 83 linear feet
  This series is divided into nine subseries. Published histories of the Pennsylvania Railroad constitute the first subseries, Histories. The remaining subseries are arranged alphabetically.
  The second and third subseries are annual reports of the parent company, 1847-1966, and of the parent and its subsidiaries, 1905-1916, 1918-1935, and 1937. Bylaws and Organization consists of several sets of bylaws from the period 1893 to 1922.
  The General Manager - Western Region subseries (boxes 184-191) includes correspondence, agreements, specifications, plans, maps, photographs, and legal papers related to the Muskegon to Milwaukee car ferry. Also in this subseries are Locality Files of the Grand Rapids Division, consisting primarily of correspondence, memoranda, and agreements having to do with improvements or abandonment of equipment, facilities, and stations in Michigan and Indiana towns and cities.
  The Miscellaneous subseries (box 183; listed as part of description for box 191) contains timetables, a 1956 hiring manual, and a 1946 report, "The Growth of Highway Traffic in Michigan." The Superintendent--Toledo Division subseries (boxes 192-195) consists of locality files for Detroit, Toledo, and various Ohio towns and subject files containing studies, maps, diagrams, rules, instructions, and other material.
  The Vice-President and General Counsel subseries (boxes 195-197) is comprised of the legal department's car ferry files, which include some photographs, and miscellaneous files including reports, agreements, a court opinion, and a history of the Eastern Division of the Central Region, Pennsylvania Railroad.
  Pennsylvania Railroad Company: Subsidiaries (boxes 198-247) is the final subseries and contains minutes, ledgers, journals, annual reports, and, occasionally, correspondence of railroads in which the Pennsylvania held a majority interest. Of these, the richest files are those of the Grand Rapids and Indiana Railroad, incorporated in 1855, and the Mackinac Transportation Company. Records of the latter are concerned with the company's applications to the Interstate Commerce Commission to abandon car ferry service; some photographs are included.
  - Histories/Other Publications
    - Corporate History of the Pennsylvania Lines West of Pittsburgh by S.H. Church (1898-1927)
      - Volumes I-VI, 6 volumes (Box 155)
      - Volumes VII-XI, 5 volumes (Box 156)
      - Volumes XII-XV, 4 volumes (Box 157)
      - Index to Volumes I-XII, 1 volumes (Box 157)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Construction and Financial History, Volumes I-IV (Box 60)
      (microfilm reel, unnumbered)
    - Centennial History of the Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1846-1946 by George H. Burgess and Miles C. Kennedy, 1949 (Box 183)
    - The Growth and Development of the Pennsylvania Railroad Company by H.W. Schotter (1927) (Box 183)
    - Hiring Manual, 1956 (Box 183)
    - Report: "Growth of Highway Traffic in Michigan," by C.B. Breed, 1946 (Box 183)
    - Timetables
      - 1922, 1923; 1927; 1929 (Box 183)
      - 1932-1935, 1937-1940 (Box 183)
      - 1941-1944 (Box 183)
      - 1946-1949 (Box 183)
      - 1950-1954 (Box 183)
      - 1955-1961 (Box 183)
  - Annual Reports
    - 1847-1880, 6 volumes (Box 165)
    - 1881-1891, 4 volumes (Box 166)
    - 1892-1901, 7 items (Box 167)
    - 1902-1910, 3 volumes (Box 168)
    - 1911-1919, 5 items (Box 169)
    - 1920-1939, 20 items (Box 170)
    - 1940-1966, 27 items (Box 171)
  - Annual Reports of Pennsylvania Railroad and Controlled Lines East and West of Pittsburgh
    - 1905-1906, 2 volumes (Box 172)
    - 1907-1908, 2 volumes (Box 173)
    - 1909-1910, 2 volumes (Box 174)
    - 1911-1912, 2 volumes (Box 175)
    - 1913-1914, 2 volumes (Box 176)
    - 1915-1916, 1918; 3 volumes (Box 177)
    - 1919-1921, 3 volumes (Box 178)
    - 1922-1925, 4 volumes (Box 179)
    - 1926-1929, 4 volumes (Box 180)
    - 1930-1933, 4 volumes (Box 181)
    - 1934-1935, 1937; 3 volumes (Box 182)
  - Bylaws and Organization
    - 1893, 1898-1899 (Box 183)
    - 1904, 1906 (Box 183)
    - 1918, 1922 (Box 183)
  - General Manager-Western Region
    The General Manager - Western Region series (boxes 184-191) includes correspondence, agreements, specifications, plans, maps, photographs, and legal papers related to the Muskegon to Milwaukee car ferry. Also in this subseries are Locality Files of the Grand Rapids Division, consisting primarily of correspondence, memoranda, and agreements having to do with improvements or abandonment of equipment, facilities, and stations in Michigan and Indiana towns and cities.
    - Car Ferry Files (Muskegon, Michigan, to Milwaukee, Wisconsin)
      - Correspondence
        - 1920-October 1933, 14 folders (Box 184)
        - November 1933-January 1945, 16 folders (Box 185)
        - April 1945-July 1953, 6 folders (Box 186)
      - District Court Opinion--Pennsylvania Railroad Company v. United States of America and Interstate Commerce Commission, 1943 (Box 186)
      - Handbook of Information on the Port of Milwaukee, 1928 (Box 186)
      - Interstate Commerce Commission
        - Applications
          - 1931 (Box 186)
          - 1932, 3 folders (Box 186)
          - 1933 (Box 186)
          - 1948 (Box 186)
          - 1953 (Box 186)
        - Exhibits, 1932 (Box 186)
        - Exhibits and Testimony, 1932 (Box 186)
        - Testimony and Data, 1932 (Box 186)
      - Maps
        - Muskegon (with Statement of Carload Business), 1930 (Box 186)
        - Pennsylvania Lines (photocopies), 1907-1916 (scattered) (Box 186)
      - Photographs, 1930 (Box 186)
      - Plans
        - 1916 (revised, 1927 and 1928) (Box 187)
        - 1917, 1920 (revised 1923) (Box 187)
        - 1931 (Box 187)
      - Specifications for Twin Screw Steel Car Ferry, 1930-1931; 2 folders (Box 187)
      - Studies by J.W. LaRue, 1929-1936; 3 folders (Box 187)
      - Supplemental Agreement between Grand Trunk Milwaukee Car Ferry Company, Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, and Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1936 (Box 187)
    - Locality Files-Grand Rapids Division
      - Indiana
        - Kendallville
          - Rearrangement of Signals, 1925-1926 (Box 187)
        - Rome City
          - Sale or Lease of Island Property, 1921-1927 (Box 187)
        - Swan
          - Abandonment of Station Building, 1925 (Box 187)
      - Michigan
        - Alba
          - Interlocker, 1923-1933 (Box 187)
        - Bay View
          - Use of Station by Pere Marquette Railway, 1920-1930 (Box 187)
        - Big Rapids. See: Howard City, Michigan (Box 187)
        - Cadillac
          - Abandonment of Coal Dock, 1925-1942; 3 folders (Box 187)
          - New Freight House, 1920-1930; 2 folders (Box 187)
        - Childsdale
          - Retirement of Passenger Station, 1928 (Box 187)
        - Clarion
          - Change in Location of Station (Box 188)
          - Change in Name of Station, 1926-1927 (Box 188)
        - Dennis Station
          - Abandonment of Station, 1929 (Box 188)
        - Edgewater
          - Retirement of Station, 1928 (Box 188)
        - Falmouth
          - Proposed Wye Track for Handling Snow Equipment, 1926-1927 (Box 188)
        - Fuller
          - Cancellation of Agreements with Pere Marquette and Detroit, Grand Haven, and Milwaukee Railways, 1927-1929 (Box 188)
        - Grand Rapids
          - Agreement with Michigan Central, Pere Marquette, and Pennsylvania Railroads re Use of Wye Track, 1924-1925 (Box 188)
          - Agreement with Pere Marquette and Michigan Central Railroads re Use of Tracks and Property, 1926-1935; 3 folders (Box 188)
          - Club Room for Employees, 1921-1933 (Box 188)
          - Coach Yard-Blueprint, 1927 (Box 188)
          - Coal Hoist, 1926 (Box 188)
          - Coal Wharf, 1929-1941; 3 folders (Box 188)
          - Enginehouse, 1925 (Box 188)
          - Extension of Passing Sidings, 1929-1937; 2 folders (Box 188)
          - Godfrey Avenue Station, 1929 (Box 188)
          - Industries Located in the Grand Rapids and Indiana Railway Where Pere Marquette Railway Has Attempted to Obtain Entrance, 1926 (Box 188)
          - Insurance Department Inspection Reports, 1924-1933 (Box 188)
          - Interlocker at Front Street, 1929-1930 (Box 188)
          - Interlocker at Grand Trunk Crossing, Fuller, 1930-1936 (Box 188)
          - Lunch Room for Employees at Enginehouse, 1926-1927 (Box 188)
          - Power Plant
            - 1927-1932, 4 folders (Box 188)
            - 1932-1938, 4 folders (Box 189)
          - Signals, 1931 (Box 189)
          - Train Shed, 1926-1930; 2 folders (Box 189)
          - Union Station
            - Barbershop, 1929 (Box 189)
            - Joint Use of Station by New York Central, 1930 (Box 189)
            - Lamproom and Trainmen's Quarters, 1929 (Box 189)
            - Uniforms for Employees, 1926-1927 (Box 189)
            - Use of Station by United States Railway Mail Service, 1927 (Box 189)
        - Haire
          - Retirement of Depot, 1929 (Box 189)
        - Harbor Springs
          - Abandonment, 1925-1936; 2 folders (Box 189)
        - Howard City
          - Demonstration Farm, 1922-1941 (Box 189)
          - Proposed Removal of Pere Marquette Railway from Howard City and Big Rapids, 1941 (Box 189)
          - Retirement of Station and Platform, 1933 (Box 189)
        - Huntsworth
          - Engine House, 1927 (Box 189)
          - Turntable Bridge, 1928-1936 (Box 189)
        - Jennings
          - Closing of Freight and Ticket Agency, 1923-1924 (Box 189)
          - Proposed Abandonment of Jennings and Missaukee Branches, 1924-1939; 9 folders (Box 189)
        - Kalamazoo
          - Agreement with Michigan Central re Coach Servicing, 1936 (Box 189)
        - Extension of Yard, 1926 (Box 189)
        - Joint Use of Michigan Central Enginehouse, 1933 (Box 189)
        - Proposed Relocation of Railroads, 1929 (Box 189)
        - Keystone-Retirement of Station, 1928 (Box 190)
        - Leetsville
          - Changing Station to Non-Agency Station, 1925-1930 (Box 190)
        - Mackinaw City
          - Abandonment of Turntable, 1928 (Box 190)
          - Agreement with Duluth, South Shore and Atlantic; Michigan Central; and Pere Marquette Railroads and Mackinac Transportation Company re Interchange of Traffic, 1925-1934; 2 folders (Box 190)
          - Coaling Station, 1934-1935 (Box 190)
          - Retirement of Water Station, 1929 (Box 190)
          - Sale of Property on Mackinac Island to James Doud, 1925 (Box 190)
        - Menonaqua Beach
          - Retirement of Shelter and Platform, 1929 (Box 190)
        - Merritt
          - Passenger Station, 1932 (Box 190)
        - Methany
          - Retirement of Interlocker, 1930 (Box 190)
        - Michelson
          - Concerning Agreement Between Grand Rapids and Indiana Railway and Nels Michelson, 1930 (Box 190)
          - Proposed Discontinuance of Freight and Ticket Agency, 1925-1930 (Box 190)
        - Missaukee Junction
          - Abandonment of Passenger and Freight Station, 1925-1926 (Box 190)
          - Study of Revenues and Expenditures, 1928. See: Traverse City, Michigan--Study. (Box 190)
        - Muskegon
          - Agreement with Wisconsin and Michigan Transportation Company re Joint Use of Dock Property and Tracks, 1923-1930 (Box 190)
          - Construction of Dock, 1927-1930 (Box 190)
          - Improved Dock Facilities, 1927; 1939 (Box 190)
          - Location of Docks Along Lake Front, 1930-1933 (Box 190)
          - Muskegon Oil Corporation, Oil Developments, 1927-1930 (Box 190)
          - Muskegon Railway and Navigation Company
            - 1914-1920 (Box 190)
            - 1920-1923 (Box 190)
            - 1923-1925 (Box 190)
            - 1925-1926 (Box 190)
            - 1925-1927 (Box 190)
            - 1927, 2 folders (Box 190)
            - 1927-1928 (Box 190)
          - Study of Revenues and Expenses, 1928. See: Traverse City, Michigan--Study. (Box 191)
          - Trackage Rights Granted Grand Trunk Railroad, 1930-1937 (Box 191)
          - West Michigan Dock and Market Corporation, 1933 (Box 191)
        - Muskegon Heights
          - Agreement with Muskegon Railway and Navigation Company, 1923-1937 (Box 191)
        - Opdyke
          - Abandonment of Station, 1928-1930 (Box 191)
        - Paris
          - Closing of Station, 1930-1931 (Box 191)
        - Petoskey
          - Request for Surrender of Railroad Rights at Bear Creek Spur, 1926 (Box 191)
          - Retirement of Turntable and Part of Enginehouse, 1928 (Box 191)
        - Ponshewaing
          - Retirement of Passenger Station, 1928 (Box 191)
        - Ramona Park
          - Retirement of Passenger Shelter, 1928 (Box 191)
        - Reedsburg
          - Retirement of Station Building, 1927 (Box 191)
        - Reno
          - Abandonment of Non-Agency Station, 1937-1939 (Box 191)
        - Roaring Brook
          - Retirement of Passenger Station, 1928 (Box 191)
        - Ross
          - Proposed Abandonment of Freight Agency, 1924-1937 (Box 191)
        - Slights
          - Closing of Station, 1930-1931 (Box 191)
        - Traverse City
          - General, 1933-1938 (Box 191)
          - Interlocking with Pere Marquette, 1927-1930 (Box 191)
          - Kiwanis Club Request for Co-operation in Bay Frontage Beautification, 1925; 1932 (Box 191)
          - Operation of Branch by Manistee and Northeastern Railroad Company, 1926-1927 (Box 191)
          - Proposed Donation of Land to City and Improvement of Railroad Avenue, 1930 (Box 191)
          - Proposed Joint Station with Pere Marquette Railway Company, 1921-1925 (Box 191)
          - Proposed Joint Use of Pere Marquette Enginehouse, 1933 (Box 191)
          - Retirement of Buildings, 1929 (Box 191)
          - Retirement of Enginehouse, 1925 (Box 191)
          - Retirement of Fruit Dock, 1927 (Box 191)
          - Retirement of Turntable, Sandhouse and Coal Dock, 1926 (Box 191)
          - Study of Revenues and Expenses: Traverse City, Missaukee, and Muskegon Branches, 1927-1928; 5 folders (Box 191)
        - Tustin
          - Station Building, 1937 (Box 191)
        - Umlor
          - Retirement of Old Station Building, 1927 (Box 191)
        - Vicksburg
          - Joint Passenger Station-Grand Trunk, 1927 (Box 191)
          - Proposed Extension of Siding, 1936 (Box 191)
          - Reconstruction of "BU" Office, 1929-1930 (Box 191)
        - Wagner
          - Retirement of Station and Milk Platform, 1928 (Box 191)
        - Walloon Lake
          - Abandonment of Walloon Lake Branch, 1927-1929 (Box 191)
  - Superintendent-Toledo Division
    The Superintendent--Toledo Division subseries (boxes 192-195) consists of locality files for Detroit, Toledo, and various Ohio towns and subject files containing studies, maps, diagrams, rules, instructions, and other material.
    - Locality Files
      - Michigan-Detroit
        - Agreement with Canadian National Railway Company and Wabash Railway Company re Track Use in West Detroit, 1923-1925 (Box 192)
        - Agreement with Detroit, Monroe and Toledo Short Line Railway and Pere Marquette Railway re Tracks at West Fort Street, 1926-1927 (Box 192)
        - Agreements with Pere Marquette Railway Company
          - 1921-1925 (Box 192)
          - 1924-1946 (scattered) (Box 192)
        - Clark Avenue Crossing Interlocking Plant, 1927 (Box 192)
        - Congress Street Freight Platform: Complaint by Pere Marquette Railway, 1937-1940 (Box 192)
        - Ecorse Junction (River Rouge)
          - Interlocking Facilities, 1932-1936 (Box 192)
          - Telegraph Operators, 1932-1934 (Box 192)
        - Fordson: Construction of Schaefer Spur Track, 1925-1926 (Box 192)
        - Fort Street Union Depot
          - Agreements with Other Railroads, 1930-1931 (Box 192)
          - Engine Service, 1932-1934 (Box 192)
          - Expenses, 1922-1935 (Box 192)
          - Minutes of Meetings of Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1932-1938 (Box 192)
          - Public Information at Station, 1940 (Box 192)
          - Use of Third Street Team Tracks, 1929-1930 (Box 192)
        - Fullerton Avenue: Construction of Yard Tracks, 1935-1937 (Box 192)
        - Grand River Avenue Team Track Facilities, 1924-1928 (Box 192)
        - Highland Park
          - Construction of Main Line to Ford Motor Company, 1924-1926 (Box 192)
          - Construction of Track Across Oakland Avenue, 1928 (Box 192)
        - Hill Branch Extension of Track Beyond Meyers Road, 1925-1926 (Box 192)
        - Lincoln Park: Grade Separation at Outer Drive, 1932-1933 (Box 192)
        - Michigan Avenue Interlocking Plant, 1930-1931; 1936 (Box 192)
        - Oakland Avenue Grade Separation, 1924-1926 (Box 192)
        - Oakwood: Relocation of Interchange Track, 1928 (Box 192)
        - River Rouge: Tracks Along River Front, 1934 (Box 192)
        - Russell Street Freight House
          - 1925-1929 (Box 192)
          - 1928 (Box 192)
        - Sixth Street Interlocker, 1931-1932 (Box 192)
        - South Dearborn Road Grade Separation, 1924-1932 (Box 192)
        - Ternes Branch
          - Construction, 1924-1925 (Box 192)
          - Extension, 1929 (Box 192)
        - Third Street Freight Station
          - Extension, 1936-1937 (Box 192)
          - Retirement of Platform, 1940 (Box 192)
        - Twenty-first Street Bridge, 1924-1934 (Box 192)
        - Twenty-first Street Engine Terminal
          - Blueprints, 1926 (Box 192)
          - Retirement of Track, 1939 (Box 192)
        - Warren Avenue Interlocking Plant, 1933-1935 (Box 192)
        - West Belt Line
          - Construction of Track Facilities, 1927 (Box 192)
          - Extension of Tracks to Ford Motor Company's Highland Park Plant, 1929-1930 (Box 192)
          - Second Main Track Between West Chicago Avenue and Warren Avenue, 1927-1930 (Box 192)
        - West Fort Street Track Changes, 1928 (Box 192)
      - Ohio
        - Burgoon
          - Retirement of Station, 1933-1935 (Box 192)
        - Carrothers
          - Proposed Interlocking, 1924-1937; 2 folders (Box 192)
        - Coleman: Remote Control Switches, 1930-1931 (Box 193)
        - Gibsonburg
          - Electric Switch Mechanism, 1929-1935 (Box 193)
          - Telephone and Telegraph Equipment, 1932-1933 (Box 193)
          - Water Station, 1920-1939 (scattered) (Box 193)
        - Helena
          - Retirement of Station, 1939-1940 (Box 193)
          - Retirement of Track and Stock Pens, 1938 (Box 193)
        - Millersville
          - Retirement of Station, 1935-1941 (Box 193)
        - Stack
          - Interlocker, 1919-1931 (Box 193)
        - Tiffin
          - Interlocking Plant
            - 1903-1931 (scattered) (Box 193)
            - 1920-1929 (Box 193)
            - 1930-1939 (Box 193)
          - Remote Control Switches, 1930-1931 (Box 193)
          - Water Station, 1921-1940 (scattered) (Box 193)
        - Toledo
          - Bridge Number 83, East Toledo, 1920-1924 (Box 193)
          - Coy Road Grade Crossing, 1937 (Box 193)
          - Enginehouse Turntable, 1925-1929 (Box 193)
          - Grade Separations
            - 1922-1931 (Box 193)
            - 1925-1938 (Box 193)